zeekrewards.com 2012-06-30

# NewNetMail - Privacy Policy

** PRIVACY POLICY**

** \-- IMPORTANT -- PLEASE READ** 

ZeekRewards shares your concerns about personal privacy. Through the Service, and through other contact with ZeekRewards, ZeekRewards may collect personal information and data including, but not limited to, application and web site usage data, viewing data, file transfer and e-mail data, and personal contact information such as e-mail addresses, mailing addresses and phone numbers. Additionally, ZeekRewards' applications and web sites may use technological facilities for tagging and tracking including, but not limited to, Web cookies, login usernames and other technologies to track and correlate data. 

The ZeekRewards Service does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  \- we provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with ZeekRewards. These companies may use your personal information to help ZeekRewards communicate with you about offers from ZeekRewards and our marketing partners. However, we do not grant these companies any independent right to share this information. 

  \- information posted to public areas of ZeekRewards and our other affiliated sites, such as the Message Boards, Guestbooks, Home Pages, etc., may be accessed by other people and nonaffiliated companies. 

  \- You may use the permissioning features of the Service to give others access to your information, including contact information. You accept responsibility for understanding the user interface, and agree to contact ZeekRewards Support with any questions concerning these features and the interface prior to using them. You also accept that ZeekRewards has not validated user's identities, and that users may not be who they say they are. 

  \- we may separately receive information about you which we make accessible to others from sources other than you, including without limitation, directories. 

  \- we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 

  \- we believe it may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ZeekRewards' terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

  \- we transfer information about you if the ZeekRewards Service is transferred to, acquired by or merged with another company. 

We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. We sometimes release beta versions of our products, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome user feedback on any privacy concerns you may have. In light of the above and because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, ZeekRewards does not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. ZeekRewards shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this privacy policy. 

This policy may change from time to time, and any changes are binding on you. We encourage you to visit this site from time to time to review the most updated policies. 

Once you have signed up as a ZeekRewards user, even if you later cancel your user id, any personal data previously collected remains the property of ZeekRewards. 

ZeekRewards cannot guarantee the accuracy of personal data.

USE OF ZEEKREWARDS IS CONTINGENT UPON ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY,  TERMS OF SERVICE AND PURCHASE/AFFILIATE AGREEMENT.
